#### Contact

ramsgobi@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rajaramalingam-961a2922 (LinkedIn) drmramalingam.zohosites.com (Personal)

ramsphdblog.blogspot.com (Blog) easywayos.blogspot.com/2019/08/ basic-operating-system.html (Blog)

### Top Skills

Research Cluster Analysis Windows

#### **Publications**

Wireless Mobile Ad hoc Network

Cluster and Security Based Approach

"Data Mining and Warehousing: Clustering and Outlier Mining Approach", ISBN – 978-93-86638-75-5

"Computer Science Question Bank for Competitive Examinations",, ISBN- 978-939777-4-3

An Analysis on Different Orientation and Aspects of Research", ISBN -978-93-86638-05-2,

# Raja Ramalingam

Associate Professor & Head in Computer Science(Artificial Intelligence & Date Science), Gobi Arts & Science College, Gobi, Erode, TN, India, Completed PhD in Bharathiar University,2015. Erode, Tamil Nadu, India

## Summary

Currently working at Gobi Arts & Science College, Assistant Professor, Dept.of Computer Science since 2009. In 2015, I have completed PhD in Cluster Algorithm (Implemented in Mobile Ad hoc Network). I worked as a Software Engineer from 2005 to 2009, gained experience on Web Applications such as Asp, Asp.Net, RDBMS-oracle.

Area of Research: Cluster Analysis using Euclidean Distance Linear Algebra, Algorithm Design.

My passion: Teaching-Learning must be a celebration, "learning is not competition".

"Learn one thing completely then other will included "

My Vision: Teacher should be a innovator.

My Focus: Make a computer science as a Science, Technology optimist.

My blog: http://ramsphdblog.blogspot.com

https://easywayos.blogspot.com/2019/08/basic-operating-system.html

## Experience

Gobi Arts & Science College Associate Professor & Head in Computer Science(Artificial Intelligence & Date Science)

#### June 2009 - Present (14 years 10 months)

Erode Area, India

IT Industry Software Developer August 2005 - June 2009 (3 years 11 months) Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India

IT experience on ASP, ASP.net, MS Sql Server

## Education

Bharathiar University

Doctor of Philosophy - PhD, Computer Science · (2011 - 2015)

**Bharathiar University** 

M.C.A, computer applications

Gobi Arts & Science College

M.Sc - Master of Science, Computer Science

Gobi Arts & Science College

BCA - Bachelor of Computer Application, Computer Science